earnadegreenow.com 2010-01-02

# welcome to earnadegree.com

**EarnaDegreeNow PRIVACY POLICY**  
Last Revised: May 16th, 2007

This is the privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") for the Web site (“Site”) for Earn a Degree Now (“EDN”). This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information received about you when you visit our Site.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, because by visiting or using this Site, you agree to its terms. 

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we make any material change to this Privacy Policy, we will inform you by posting a notice on the home page of this Site that the policy has been updated and by changing the date on this page noting when the policy was last updated. If you see a notice of change, please check the Privacy Policy, because your continued use of the Site after we post the change means you have agreed to the new terms.

Collection of Your Data

_Personal Data_. When you fill out a “Student Matching Profile”, our Self-Assessment Tools, and at other times, we ask for some information about you, such as your name, age, email address, postal address, and phone number, level of education, desired level of educational program, areas of interest, current occupation, military status (if any), governmental loan status. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13.

_Anonymous Data_. We automatically collect IP addresses and Web site usage information from you when you visit the Site. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors use and navigate the Site on an aggregate basis, including the number and frequency of visitors to each Web page, and the length of their visits.

How We Use Your Information

We may use your personal data in the following ways:

  * For the purpose for which you specifically provided the personal data, for example to match your student matching profile to educational institutions or to respond to a specific inquiry. 
  * To send you notifications about your accounts or transactions with us and to otherwise contact you with information that we believe will be of interest to you. 
  * To notify you about our products and services and special offers. 
  * To enhance existing features or develop new features products and services. 

We may combine the information that we collect from you on the Site with information that we collect from third parties. 

Sharing Your Data

We share this personal data with the educational institutions to which we have matched your profile so that these institutions can contact you with information about their educational programs. These educational institutions are not governed by this Privacy Policy. If you want to know more about a partner school’s use of your information, contact the school directly. We may also share your personal data with other third parties whose products or services may be of interest to you. 

We also share your information with the service providers who help us to run this Site or to fulfill your requests. We may also need to disclose your personal data to third parties if required by law or to enforce our User Agreement or this Privacy Policy, or when we, in our sole discretion, believe it is necessary or appropriate, in connection with a sale or transfer of some or all of our assets in the Site. 

Your Ability To Choose

You can let us know that you do not wish us to share your information with third parties for marketing purposes or to notify you about our own products and services and special offers by [opting out at the time that you submit your Student Matching Profile or by] sending us a written request either by email to [info@earnadegreenow.com](mailto:info@earnadegreenow.com) or via postal mail: 

Attn: Unsubscribe  
Earn a Degree Now   
7969 N BLACKSTONE AVE   
FRESNO, CA 93720 \- USA

Please be aware that we do not control the activities of the educational institutions with which we match your profile or any third parties to whom we have provided your information for marketing purposes. If you wish them to stop contacting you, you will need to notify them of this fact separately. 

Cookies and Other Technology

We use cookies to allow you to move quickly through our site, to recognize repeat visitors and to allow you to take advantage of some of our site’s special features. A cookie is a string of information that is sent by a Web site and stored on your hard drive or temporarily in your computer’s memory. Cookies are small files and won’t pose any significant disk-space concerns. 

You can turn off the ability to receive any of these cookies by adjusting the browser in your computer. The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. Without cookies you can visit our Site, but you will not be able to use the services that require you to provide your personal information. 

We use clear GIFs, Web beacons, and other tracking devices to follow visitor usage of our site. The data collected through these mechanisms is anonymous, and we do not link it to the personal data you may provide us.

We use web beacons (invisible images often referred to as pixel tags or clear GIFs) on our Site in order to recognize users and assess traffic patterns. We also include Web beacons in our e-mail messages in order to count how many e-mail messages have been opened

Ads for EDN

When you view an ad for EDN on other sites, our third-party advertising company may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. EDN and our advertising company may also use Web beacons (invisible images often referred to as pixel tags or clear GIFs) to note which pages of the Site you visit after viewing our ads. The information that is collected through the use of these images is not personally identifiable and is used only to track response to our advertising efforts. 

Security

The personal data we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We will maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personal data.

Links to Other Web Sites

This Site may contain links to other Web sites. These other sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. Be sure to look for the privacy policies that govern your use of these other Web sites.

Transfer to the United States

If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the personal data you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. Whenever you submit any personal data to us, you consent to this transfer.

Review and Correction

You may review and update the personal data you have provided to us contacting us by phone by sending us written notice via postal mail to: 

Attn: Information Inquiry or Update  
Earn a Degree Now  
7969 N BLACKSTONE AVE   
FRESNO, CA 93720 - USA

Any revisions you provide to your personal data will be applied in our own records but will not be updated in the records of the educational institutions to which we have already provided your data. If you would like to review and correct the personal data that has been provided to educational institutions, you will need to contact them separately.
